{
    "Entertaiment": [{
            "id": 1,
            "question": "Who is the most followed person on instagram?",
            "Answer": "Cristiano Ronaldo",
            "option1": "Airana Grande",
            "option2": "Kylie Jenner",
            "option3": "Lionel Messi",
            "weight": 1
        },
        {
            "id": 2,
            "question": "Which of the following indian has won the oscar? ",
            "Answer": "Satyajit Ray",
            "option1": "Priyadarshan",
            "option2": "Yash Chopra",
            "option3": "Anurag Kashyap",
            "weight": 1
        },
        {
            "id": 3,
            "question": "Which is the highest grossing movie in india?",
            "Answer": "Avengers:Endgame",
            "option1": "Avengers:Infinity War",
            "option2": "The Jungle Book",
            "option3": "FF8",
            "weight": 1
        },
        {
            "id": 4,
            "question": "Which of the following indian actor has shared sliver screen with tom cruise?",
            "Answer": "Anil Kapoor",
            "option1": "Akshay Kumar",
            "option2": "Anupam Kher",
            "option3": "Irrfan Khan",
            "weight": 1
        },
        {
            "id": 5,
            "question": "Which of the following movie was released in theaters?",
            "Answer": "Ramprasad ki tehrvi",
            "option1": "Gulabo Sitabo",
            "option2": "Laxmi bomb",
            "option3": "Ludo",
            "weight": 1
        },
        {
            "id": 6,
            "question": "Aishwarya Rai was crowned Miss World in which year?",
            "Answer": "1994",
            "option1": "1995",
            "option2": "1993",
            "option3": "1996",
            "weight": 1
        },
        {
            "id": 7,
            "question": "Who is known as the 'father of Indian Cinema'",
            "Answer": "Dadasaheb Phalke",
            "option1": "Dadasaheb Torne",
            "option2": "Satyajit Ray",
            "option3": "V. Shantaram",
            "weight": 1
        },
        {
            "id": 8,
            "question": "Lata Mangeshkar awarded with Bharat Ratna in the year",
            "Answer": "2001",
            "option1": "1998",
            "option2": "2003",
            "option3": "2005",
            "weight": 1
        },
        {
            "id": 9,
            "question": "Real name of Rajnikant?",
            "Answer": "Shivaji Rao Gaekwad",
            "option1": "Shivaji Rao Deshmukh",
            "option2": "Shivaji Rao ",
            "option3": "Shivaji ",
            "weight": 1
        },
        {
            "id": 10,
            "question": "Who is the first indian movie star to be featured on the cover of Time magazine",
            "Answer": "parveen Babi",
            "option1": "Zeenat Aman",
            "option2": "Amir Khan",
            "option3": "Aishwarya Rai",
            "weight": 1
        }
    ],
    "com": [{
            "id": 1,
            "question": "Ctrl, Shift and Alt are called .......... keys.",
            "Answer": "modifier",
            "option2": "function",
            "option3": "adjustment",
            "option1": "alphanumeric",
            "weight": 1
        },
        {
            "id": 2,
            "question": "MS-Word is an example of _____",
            "option1": "An operating system",
            "option2": "A processing device",
            "Answer": "Application software",
            "option3": "An input device",
            "weight": 1
        },
        {
            "id": 3,
            "question": "A computer cannot 'boot' if it does not have the _____",
            "option1": "Compiler",
            "option2": "Loader",
            "Answer": "Operating System",
            "option3": "Assembler",
            "weight": 1
        },
        {
            "id": 4,
            "question": "By default, your documents print in ________ mode",
            "option1": "Landscape",
            "Answer": "Portrait",
            "option3": "Page Setup",
            "option2": "Print View",
            "weight": 1
        },
        {
            "id": 5,
            "question": "Which of the following is a popular programming language for developing multimedia webpages",
            "option1": "COBOL",
            "Answer": "Java",
            "option3": "Basic",
            "option2": "Assembler",
            "weight": 1
        },
        {
            "id": 6,
            "question": "The first computer was programmed using .......",
            "option1": "Assembly language",
            "Answer": "Machine Language",
            "option3": "Spaghetti code",
            "option2": "Source code",
            "weight": 1
        },
        {
            "id": 7,
            "question": "The computer's processor consists of the following parts",
            "option1": "CPU and Main memory",
            "option2": "Hard Disk and Floppy Drive",
            "Answer": "Control Unit and ALU",
            "option3": "OS and Application",
            "weight": 1
        },
        {
            "id": 8,
            "question": "A _______ is a software program used to view Web pages.",
            "option1": "site",
            "option2": "host",
            "option3": "link",
            "Answer": "browser",
            "weight": 1
        },
        {
            "id": 9,
            "question": "Where is RAM located?",
            "Answer": "Mother Board",
            "option2": "Expansion Board",
            "option3": "External Drive",
            "option1": "None",
            "weight": 1
        },
        {
            "id": 10,
            "question": "Which key is used in combination with another key to perform a specific task?",
            "option1": "Function",
            "option2": "Spacebar",
            "option3": "Arrow",
            "Answer": "Control",
            "weight": 1
        }
    ],
    "lit": [{
        "id": 1,
        "question": "Who among the following writers won the 2017 Sahitya Academy Award for Hindi literature?",
        "option1": "Niranjan Mishra",
        "Answer": "Ramesh Kuntal Megh",
        "option3": "Uday Narayana Singh",
        "option2": "Shrikant Deshmukh",
        "weight": 1
    },
    {
        "id": 2,
        "question": "Name the first Indian to get Nobel prize in literature.",
        "option1": "Amartya Sen",
        "option2": "Lal Bahadur Shastri",
        "option3": "CV Raman",
        "Answer": "Rabindranath Tagore",
        "weight": 1
    },
    {
        "id": 3,
        "question": "Which of the following awards is given in the field of literature?",
        "option1": "Arjuna Award",
        "option2": "Ashok Chakra",
        "Answer": "Vyas Samman",
        "option3": "Bharat Award",
        "weight": 1
    },
    {
        "id": 4,
        "question": "The religious literature of the Jain at the early stage was written in",
        "Answer": "Ardhamagadhi",
        "option2": "Pali",
        "option3": "Sanskrit",
        "option1": "None",
        "weight": 1
    },
    {
        "id": 5,
        "question": "Who among the following has not received a Nobel Prize in literature",
        "option1": "Derek Walcott",
        "option2": "Pablo Neruda",
        "Answer": "Churchill",
        "option3": "Ernest Hemingway",
        "weight": 1
    },
    {
        "id": 6,
        "question": "Which poet is considered a national hero in Greece?",
        "option1": "John Keats",
        "Answer": "Lord Byron",
        "option3": "Solan",
        "option2": "Sappho",
        "weight": 1
    },
    {
        "id": 7,
        "question": "Rupert Brooke wrote his poetry during which conflict?",
        "option1": "Boer War",
        "option2": "Second World War",
        "option3": "Korean War",
        "Answer": "First World War",
        "weight": 1
    },
    {
        "id": 8,
        "question": "A pattern of accented and unaccented syllables in lines of poetry",
        "option1": "rhyme scheme",
        "Answer": "meter",
        "option3": "rhythm",
        "option2": "rhyme",
        "weight": 1
    },
    {
        "id": 9,
        "question": "Applying human qualities to non-human things",
        "Answer": "personification",
        "option2": "onomatopoeia",
        "option3": "alliteration",
        "option1": "metaphor",
        "weight": 1
    },
    {
        "id": 10,
        "question": "A poem that tells a story with plot, setting, and characters",
        "option1": "lyric",
        "option2": "free verse",
        "Answer": "narrative",
        "option3": "node",
        "weight": 1
    }
    ],
    "sport": [{
        "id": 1,
        "question": "Rovers Cup is related to which of the following sports?",
        "Answer": "Football",
        "option2": "Cricket",
        "option3": "Hockey",
        "option1": "Tennis",
        "weight": 1
    },
    {
        "id": 2,
        "question": "Who is the President of International World Games Association?",
        "Answer": "Jose Perurena Lopez",
        "option2": "Andrew Parsons",
        "option3": "Duane Kale",
        "option1": "Robert Steadward",
        "weight": 1
    },
    {
        "id": 3,
        "question": "How many teams had participated in the 2018 Womenâ€™s Hockey World Cup?",
        "option1": "8",
        "Answer": "16",
        "option3": "22",
        "option2": "20",
        "weight": 1
    },
    {
        "id": 4,
        "question": "Which Indian cricketer has scored the maximum runs in ODIs?",
        "option1": "Kapil Dev",
        "option2": "Sunil Gavaskar",
        "Answer": "Sachin Tendulkar",
        "option3": "Virat Kohli",
        "weight": 1
    },
    {
        "id": 5,
        "question": "Which is first Indian cricket tournament ?",
        "option1": "Bombey Series",
        "option2": "Pepsi Cup",
        "Answer": "Bombay Triangular",
        "option3": "None",
        "weight": 1
    },
    {
        "id": 6,
        "question": "Which of the following is first cricket club in India ?",
        "Answer": "Oriental Cricket Club",
        "option2": "Maharashtra Cricket Club",
        "option3": "East Indian Cricket Club",
        "option1": "Bombay Cricket Club",
        "weight": 1
    },
    {
        "id": 7,
        "question": "Indian played their First T20 Match against _______.",
        "Answer": "South Africa",
        "option2": "Australia",
        "option3": "England",
        "option1": "Pakistan",
        "weight": 1
    },
    {
        "id": 8,
        "question": "Total no. of players playing on the pitch in a hockey match is?",
        "Answer": "22",
        "option2": "16",
        "option3": "20",
        "option1": "18",
        "weight": 1
    },
    {
        "id": 9,
        "question": "The dimensions of a Hockey field are?",
        "Answer": "91.4m X 55m",
        "option2": "92m X 55m",
        "option3": "92.5m X 56m",
        "option1": "91.4m X 56m",
        "weight": 1
    },
    {
        "id": 10,
        "question": "Name the nation that won 2014 Kabaddi World Cup Men's title.",
        "Answer": "India",
        "option2": "Bangladesh",
        "option3": "Japan",
        "option1": "Pakistan",
        "weight": 1
    }
    ],
    "gk": [{
        "id": 1,
        "question": "In which place in India can we find cave temples of three faiths?",
        "option1": "Agra",
        "Answer": "Ellora",
        "option3": "Delhi",
        "option2": "Madhurai",
        "weight": 1
    },
    {
        "id": 2,
        "question": "Which foreign influence is seen in the rock cut architecture of India?",
        "option1": "Indo-European",
        "option2": "Greek",
        "option3": "Arabic",
        "Answer": "Persian",
        "weight": 1
    },
    {
        "id": 3,
        "question": "Which of these cities has the maximum number of historical monuments?",
        "option1": "Mumbai",
        "Answer": "Delhi",
        "option3": "Kolkata",
        "option2": "Punjab",
        "weight": 1
    },
    {
        "id": 4,
        "question": "Which monument was built in memory of a British monarch?",
        "option1": "King Richard Memorial",
        "option2": "Prince of Wales Memorial",
        "option3": "King George Memorial",
        "Answer": "Victoria Memorial",
        "weight": 1
    },
    {
        "id": 5,
        "question": "Everyone knows 'The Taj Mahal'. It was built by the Emperor Shah Jahan, but for whom?",
        "option1": "Farida Mahal",
        "Answer": "Mumtaz Mahal",
        "option3": "Jahani Mahal",
        "option2": "Toba Begum",
        "weight": 1
    },
    {
        "id": 6,
        "question": "Which city in India has built a 15.8 m high 'Gandhi Stupa' dedicated to Mahatma Gandhi?",
        "option1": "Allahbad, UP",
        "option2": "Varodara, Gujarat",
        "option3": "Ranchi, Jharkhand",
        "Answer": "Vijaywada, AP",
        "weight": 1
    },
    {
        "id": 7,
        "question": "The architecture of the city of Cochin in Kerala reflects the influence of...?",
        "option1": "The Dutch",
        "option2": "The Portuguese",
        "option3": "The British",
        "Answer": "All of these",
        "weight": 1
    },
    {
        "id": 8,
        "question": "Where is the world's largest panoramic sculptural relief located?",
        "option1": "Pondicherry",
        "option2": "Kanchipuram",
        "option3": "Mahabalipuram",
        "Answer": "Madhurai",
        "weight": 1
    },
    {
        "id": 9,
        "question": "In which Indian city would you find the mosque with 'Shaking Minarets'?",
        "option1": "Allahbad",
        "option2": "Hyderabad",
        "option3": "Lucknow",
        "Answer": "Ahmedabad",
        "weight": 1
    },
    {
        "id": 10,
        "question": "Which state is known as India's Spice Garden...?",
        "option1": "Bihar",
        "Answer": "Kerela",
        "option3": "Uttaranchal",
        "option2": "Karnataka",
        "weight": 1
    }
    ],
  
    "users": [{
        "username": "abcd",
        "email": "jdfkihdf",
        "password": "4444",
        "result": "1",
        "id": "id"
    }],
    "subject_data": [{
        "username": "abcd",
        "subject_name": "lit",
        "highest_score": "23",
        "no_of_times_attempted": "3",
        "total_ques": 12,
        "max_marks": 12,
        "id": 1
    }],
    "new": [
        {}
    ]
  }